I'm in a seal show. Today's big up, big up doesn't exist because we have two letdowns today.
Letdowns.
Goes to Tesla and backing out of a big order of mini pies.
So this place called the Given Pies, a black owned bakery in San Jose,
they got an order from Tesla for 4,000 mini pies.
They made the pies and then they just canceled it.
The bakery sent them a quote, the order was approved.
They started making the pies and they got a text canceling the order.
They had bought all these additional ingredients.
They had like changed their production schedules.
They had turned down other Black History Month catering requests to fulfill Tesla's needs.
Like, come on, that's not okay.
You know what else isn't cool?
Lack of accountability goes to Madonna.
Madonna is on her celebration tour.
During the show, she features a well-intentioned AIDS tribute to her friends and peers that,
you know, we've lost to the disease.
However, she included somebody that has not been confirmed as having succumbed to the disease.
And sometimes it is never too much.
Yes, it is too much.
When you include Luther Vandross in a tribute.
I like that, yes.
I mean, what are we?
Luther Vandross died in 2005 due to complications from a stroke.
And Madonna is pretty sharp.
But she missed the mark on this one.
Her house was not a home.
We are, we are, we are.